Thank you for watching!
Yukkana Ukka Showroom in Ukka
Yay!
Good evening, everyone.
This is Uka.
Today's show will be led by
I, Awa Yururi, will be your host today.
I look forward to working with you.
Yoo, please introduce yourself.
Yes, I'm Yu Iwasawa.
Good evening.
I'm Koharu Wakana.
These three of us will be presenting this time.
I look forward to working with you.
This is the 200th showroom called "Ukka no Yukai" to commemorate this occasion.
Yay!
I am happy that the three of us are celebrating our 200th showroom together.
I'm so happy.
Mr. Sorashido threw a tower for us right away.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much, Mr. Sorashido.
Now, I would like to have a spread time here.
Yes, I'm going to do it.
In order for many people to see this distribution, I'm going to send an announcement post with X, so please spread the word.
Please spread the word.
Do you have any suggestions for the poses and comments?
Isn't it 200 times today?
Yes, I think so.
So why don't the three of us make 200?
Okay.
Let's do it.
Which one of us should make 2?
I think it's 2 for Kawari-chan.
Yes, that's right.
Yes, that's right. Yes, I do.
So I'm 2.
200, oh, like this.
Two is a bit tricky.
Like this?
What would you like for your fans?
I like it a lot, a lot, a lot.
What do you do for your fans?
Oh, but I'm so happy for them.
Like, "Congratulations on 200 times.
Well, please comment on the 200 congratulations to the fans.
We're all set, so good night.
If you type 200 congratulations, I'd like to start tissue time.
Yes, sir.
Oh, I think we're getting there a little bit soon, don't you?
Yes, they are.
They're here.
Then, please take a shot.
Please do.
200 yen, 200 yen, 200 yen, 200 yen, 200 yen.
How's that sound? Good? Okay, five, four, three, two, one. Thank you.
Okay, everyone, the official Ukka X account will be sending out these screenshots,
So please post lots of announcements on X. Please, please, please, please.
Please do. Now, let's get right to the planning.
A report on a fun and foo-foo one-man live concert.
Yes, it's like this is what we are going to do today, isn't it? Yes, I am.
On January 21, you held your first one-man live concert, NEW CHAPTER 7, at Liquid Room in Ebisu, Tokyo.
Thank you very much to everyone who came and watched the live streaming. Thank you very much.
How was your first time on stage as Ukka?
It was a lot of fun.
I heard it was a lot of work, so let's start with the lesson.
Let's start with the lesson.
From the lesson.
Lesson section.
Lesson... I don't know how to say it.
Lesson... We started out with just the two of us, and then we started choreographing the lesson, We started with just the two of us, and then we started choreographing,
Then, the older sisters came to teach us,
I don't know, about two months later, when the seven of us started taking lessons together,
Well, but even among the members,
I was very nervous.
When we met? When we met.
You were nervous?
I wondered what the lessons would be like.
The atmosphere of the lesson is different in each group.
Well, that's true.
How was it? Were you comfortable? Are you okay? No, I'm not.
Are you okay? Were you scared? Are you okay?
It was comfortable.
Good, good, good, good.
Oh, really? How about you, Yu-chan?
I've already had a hard time being free.
No, no, no, I mean..,
21 songs?
A lot.
But, no, not really,
How many months of time did you have?
September?
September.
Because it started in September,
September, October, November, December,
About five months.
I had lessons for about five months,
I worked very hard.
I worked hard, didn't I?
You know, during the five months,
You had lessons with the research students.
And you also had school, so it must have been hard.
Yes, it was.
It was hard, wasn't it?
But it was fun and fulfilling.
On the contrary?
Yes. I'm the type of person who doesn't know what to do in my free time.
That's why I always sleep when I come back to school. So, when I came back to school, I was always in bed.
But after school, I had a lot of lessons, so I would leave the house right after school,
So, for me, it was very fulfilling. It was real fulfilling.
Was it real fulfilling? A little more.
Yes, I was.
I was very fulfilled in real life.
I was very satisfied with my life. I'm glad.
I'm glad.
Yes, I am. I know the lessons were tough, but both of them worked really hard and didn't show any signs of weakness,
I was actually very happy. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Yes, the day before the 21st. Did you sleep well the day before?
Ah! Why don't you make a rehearsal version?
Oh, sure. Oh, you want to put a rehearsal in between?
Yes, that's a good idea.
That's a good idea. A rehearsal. You've done a rehearsal for the first time?
Yes, I did.
There is a rehearsal called "genepro," where you go through the live performance, including the MC, and this was the first genepro for the two of you.
When we were research students, we had a rehearsal called "genepro," but we had never seen a live performance with a microphone, speakers in front of us, or even in costume, so I was very surprised.
I was very surprised to see the microphone, as I expected.
Yes, yes.
It was the first time for me to see the width and length of a live venue, so it was very interesting.
Was it fresh?
It was fresh.
Oh, good, good.
But it was the first time for me to put on an earpiece, and since I had never done it before, I was a little worried about whether I could sing well or not, because it felt really strange.
It's different, isn't it?
It's different.
It's like something and nothing.
It's totally different.
Yes, it is.
But what did you think when you made the ear monitors?
How did you feel when you made the ear monitors?
Ear monitors are made by putting a piece of clay in your ear, moving it around a little bit, and then taking it off when it hardens, and then telling it to the craftsman. Did you feel it?
Did you feel the sensation of having someone like an earplug on your ear? You know, the ones that look like earplugs on top of them?
Yeah.
I had never really worn earplugs before, so I thought, "What? Won't my ears fall down? Won't you lose touch with them? I remember thinking that.
What do you think?
I probably laughed the whole time.
On the contrary, did you two go together?
We went together.
We went together, and while I was being fucked the whole time, she kept giggling and asking me, are you okay? Does it hurt? I felt like I was making them worry.
I was kind of ticklish and laughed the whole time.
I see.
I guess there were a lot of changes in the environment, such as wearing earphones for the first time. Even just during this rehearsal period.
Yes.
The day before the day of the concert?
The day before the day of the concert.
The day before the day of the concert. How was it?
The day before, you had a lesson, right?
Yeah, yeah.
After the lesson, did you eat and sleep well?
I went to bed, but I slept, woke up, went to bed, woke up, went to bed, woke up, and so on.
I went to bed, woke up, went to bed, woke up, woke up.
I repeated that three times. I was too nervous.
You didn't sleep well.
That's right.
I see.
You are not tired at all.
Not at all.
Are you all right?
Yes, I am.
I see.
Did you get a good night's sleep?
I slept well, but I felt like it all happened so fast.
The most important thing for me was the fact that tomorrow is the big day.
It all happened so fast, didn't it?
But from January to the concert, from New Year's to the concert, it seemed like only one second had passed.
It was like only one minute had passed.
Really.
Indeed.
For sure. Certainly.
Certainly.
Really, really.
It was a moment.
It was pretty packed with a lot of things, right at the end, wasn't it?
Yeah.
To solidify and so on. So, it all happened so fast. If you were doing various things, right?
Yes, it was.
That's for sure.
I don't know, time passed before I knew it.
Yes, it did.
It all happened so fast. Until the day before.
Yes, until the day before.
Until the day before.
Yes.
It was like this. Yes, then, the day of the event.
On the day.
The day of the event.
Now that the day has finally arrived, how was it? Well, first of all, before the show.
Before the show.
How did you feel before the show?
Before the show, I didn't know what to expect.
I had no idea how many people would be there, or how they would feel about coming to the show.
I didn't know how many people would be there, or when, or how they would feel, so I was pretty nervous.
I was quite nervous. I was not.
I was very nervous.
I don't. I don't. I don't. I don't.
I didn't. I didn't. I didn't. I didn't.
I didn't do it because I had finally arrived, but I was very nervous until I stood up,
Well, I was tied up in that small room for a long time.
The small room in the back.
It's a small room at the back of the room.
I see. I see.
How about you, Ri-chan?
Oh, but at the rehearsal, I was nervous too, but the rehearsal was..,
It was a lot of fun, a lot of fun...
With Daigo and Daigo and Daigo...
I didn't get too nervous, I was able to do it as usual.
Just like we always do.
Yeah, yeah.
Is it the same with you?
Yes, I was.
That's important. But there was surprisingly little time.
So I had the impression that things were very rushed.
I've been to many one-man shows, and I've been to many one-man shows, but I never have enough time.
I wonder what that is about. So I don't have any more time from now on. Probably.
Definitely.
Spring and the rest of the year will start in the near future, but I definitely don't have time.
Yeah, it really goes by fast. It really goes by so fast.
You were free to wear your hair any way you wanted this time, weren't you?
Yes, I did.
Yu-chan, you were really worried about your hair style for the show.
You looked like a mother the whole time.
That's right.
Yes, that's right.
Sometimes, I thought my hair style was the prescribed hairstyle, so I just went with it,
Then, suddenly, the media told me that I was free to do my hair any way I wanted.
What?
I immediately sent a message to my mother.
So I immediately sent a message to my mother,
But she didn't respond right away,
She must have been in a rush. I'm sure so.
I didn't feel that way.
She didn't reply, so I had to ask my fans.
And one of them told me to ask Sora-chan.
So I asked Sora-chan. Then she gave me a fist bump.
Yes, yes, yes. Here it is.
Here.So this is it.
Yes, yes. I was pressed by Kobushimaru here,
And then Moa-chan also pressed my Kobushimaru, but I felt that Kobushimaru was a little different.
I had a feeling that Kobushimaru was the way to go.
It was more sensational than Kobushimaru.
It was Kobushimaru, but something was different.
I thought it was different. It didn't fit.
So I called my mom because I couldn't even get her to read my line.
And when I did, I didn't expect her to wake up from sleep.
Mom was asleep.
Mom was asleep. And the person across the street was like, what? Like, "What?
She was sleeping behind me, so I woke her up.
And the mother thought that there was an emergency among the children who suddenly called her,
That's true.
She was really worried about me, and asked me what I should do about my hair.
What? My hair? I told her I was sorry, I was sleeping, and I cut it off.
You cut it off?
That's right. Sora-chan pushed me to braid the braids we did at the concert, and that's what I ended up doing.
I see.
Yes, I see.
It totally looked good on you.
Yes, it did. I'm indecisive.
Oh, sure. You are surprisingly indecisive.
Yes, I am. Indecisive.
You are really worried about it.
I was really worried about it.
Yes.
Mamoru, you decided very quickly, didn't you?
Yes, I did. I'm a bobber, so I said to Minachan, "Minachan, what are you going to do?" and we decided soon after I said it.
I see. Surprisingly, you're the target, huh? I was so indecisive that he made up his mind so quickly.
Indeed.
I feel it's a side of Arosa. To us.
I see.
Koharu seems to be more indecisive, don't you think?
Is that so?
I'm quite indecisive.
Huh? Huh? Huh?
Are you with me by any chance? Maybe they were together?
I'm sorry.
Which one is it, Ruri?
I, uh, I might have trouble with my hair too. You know, with the members, we don't have member's colors, so I have to be careful not to wear the same color as the other members.
Hee....
What did I do? I'm like, "What did you do?
Yes, that's right.
I was able to decide rather smoothly this time. It's hot, so I want to raise it.
Ah.
That's right. That's why I decided on the ponytail right away.
That's how I felt before the day of the show.
Yes.
Yes. So we were in a hurry to get ready for the show.
How was it?
Your first time on stage as Ukha?
But I guess it's the first time I'm not allowed to do this.
I'm actually, actually...
It's just here, isn't it?
Yes.
The moment Yu-chan came on, I was like, "It's going to start already," and I started crying.
It was the first information to be released.
Tears. Yu-chan's tears.
That's right.
I saw it. Your tears.
I saw them too.
You saw it?
I saw it when I was in the back.
Auntie started to flow, and in the back, we were all hitting each other like this, and Yu-chan was holding her hands like this. Yu-chan was so upset that she said, "If I press this button, I'm going to cry.
If I press the bottom of the top.
Yes, she was singing to her aunt.
She was singing to her aunt, and she was like, "What should I do, what should I do, my heart is about to give out.
Then, when I felt a "fha" sound, I took a deep breath and cried.
I started to loose tears.
I became loose, and then the tears started to come out.
I see. It was Leah's tears, Yu-chan. I see. It was Leah's Yu-chan's tears.
I wonder if I can see it, in the future.
I wonder.
Huh? It hurts.
It's like this. It's nerve-wracking, isn't it?
Yes.
And you don't know what kind of atmosphere you're going to have, so it's even more so when it's your first time. That's why there were quite a few songs.
Yes, there were. There were.
Yes, there were.
But the moment you came out, the depth was amazing.
Yes, yes, yes.
The depth of the fan.
Yes, yes. So I was surprised because I didn't think there would be that many people. First of all.
That's right. Because I want to thank you all for selling out the show.
Thank you very much.
I'm very happy.
So many people saw our first story together, right?
Yes, they did. And also on Nico Live.
And there was also a live broadcast.
That's right. That's right.
You can still watch the archives.
Please do.
How was it, Koharu?
I don't know.
I still don't remember the first time I saw my grandmother.
I don't remember anything about my first grandmother.
I was so excited when I saw the audience, but the next song is going to be connected with your grandmother,
I was so excited to see the audience.
When I was going to the next song, I was a bit blank and went in a strange direction, but Minachan told me it was this way.
You told me? That was amazing.
Did you understand?
I didn't notice at all.
I was trying to decide if I noticed it or not.
Why?
My back.
Back?
Oh, my God, Mina-chan, you're so cool. Oh, my God, Mina-chan, you're so cool.
Cool.
So, let's get you settled in there.
Did you put in a song?
We got one song in.
Oh, good.
I made a little bit of a mistake on the first move, but it's okay.
But don't worry, we'll get it right after the first song.
It's okay.
That's good, that's good, that's good.
The first song was to connect, right?
Yes, the first song.
It's a song to connect.
It's one song, right?
I guess it's like this. During the show.
Yeah.
I was surprised to hear the fans' reaction to this song. I was surprised to hear the reaction of the fans to this song.
There are a lot of them.
Was there? What?
There are two more songs from Viva La Vida,
Say it again.
Viva La Vida.
Viva, Vida?
Viva La Vida,
I don't want to lose.
I don't want to lose to the person I was that day.
Ta-la-la-la-la-la-la.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I don't know...it's not that.
Somehow, it's not that one.
Mobile, Wi-Fi,
Ev- Ev-.
Like a mobile battery. That's what he said.
Like Wiper.
Fiber Wiper Wiper Yeah, like Tiger.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Like that, Tiger.
Mobile Phi,
Like Mobile Tiger Fire.
I understand. I know what you mean.
Like Wiper Wiper.
Yes.
What did you say? Gentlemen.
No, what did you say?
Are you saying "mobile battery"?
Wiper-
What are you saying?
I'm Meat Boy.
Meat?
I was looking at the archives for a reminder.
I was looking at it, but it doesn't sound like a mobile battery.
I don't even know what I'm looking at.
I looked at it a couple of times and it just sounded like a mobile battery.
It's hard to tell, what's he saying.
Yettai is the fiber.
Yettai seems to be Five Wiper.
Five Wiper.
So mobile is.
Yettai is Five Wiper.
Something close.
So say I don't want to lose.
Then sing.
I don't want to lose to that person's self.
Yettai is a five-wiper.
I don't know, I can't get this rhythm.
I don't want to lose, that's who I am.
Yettai is a five-wiper.
I'm already starting with Viva la viva la viva.
Viva la beater. Viva la beater.
Muzzy, isn't it, this curl.
I can't tell you how many times I've heard it, and I really don't know what you're saying, vividly,
I can't say it myself.
I can't say it.
I really can't.
What's the other one?
The last one at 8:05.
Yes, yes, yes.
8:05.
Ta-da, ta-da, ta-da, ta-da, ta-da.
Good cod.
There is.
After all.
I can't manage it.
It's cute.
Like that.
The Gachi-Koi factory took place, right?
At 8:05.
You could hear that.
You like it, don't you?
I could hear it.
I love it.
I've gotten into the habit of singing it all the time.
I keep singing that side.
It hasn't been 8:05 yet.
I want to try it.
I've been singing.
I've been singing all the time.
So that's how it is.
I wonder what people are saying there.
You know...
What did I say?
I have something to say.
I knew it.
Who is it?
I'm sure. Indeed.
It's pretty.
You're saying "somewhere"?
Yeah.
A guess name.
I'm curious if you have a guess name.
Tell me, everyone.
Which one is everyone saying?
Where is it?
What is it?
Well...
Um...
I'm asking you.
I want to ask you something.
What?
Gachikoi.
Do you want to try it?
Gachikoi Factory?
Factory.
I've never been there.
So...
On this side.
I've never been,
I'd like to go there.
I want to go there.
Me.
Let's do it together.
With a pink penra.
In the middle of dancing,
Oh, my God.
I'm going to dance with the fans.
On the contrary.
Well, it's different to say. Well, it's different to say.
Don't dance alone.
I want to ask you something.
What are you saying?
Move, move, move.
Move. Move.
Where is it?
Even just now,
He commented that it was a guesser's name.
I see.
There were people who commented on it,
And there are others,
Yes.
There were also those who said "Ukka",
So there are all kinds of people.
Yes.
There are a lot of people who call me "ukka,
There are many.
Many.
Thank you very much.
I'm grateful.
I'm glad.
Mm-hmm.
And your voice, too, for the first time,
I could hear it,
Cole?
Sure, it's a call song.
You didn't?
Me?
I didn't?
What?
I wonder.
Hmmm...
But, you know, the most exciting song was Koznick Float, wasn't it? Wasn't it good? I didn't know it was that exciting. It was such an uplifting song, wasn't it? Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. But, you know, the most exciting song was Koznick Float, wasn't it? Wasn't it good? Wasn't it good? It was such an uplifting song, wasn't it? Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
But I don't know.
Everybody Wannabe was like the last song, like it was the last song.
It was like the last song of Everybody Wannabe.
Did you feel the passion?
Yes, I felt the passion.
Many people like Everybody Wannabe during the live performance,
I have an image of everybody. I have an image of them being passionate.
And LINDBERG, I had dreamed of them for a long time.
I used to do that kind of call, so it was a dream come true for me,
I was happy to hear it. I was happy to hear it.
I was happy.
It was the first time I was called out for a song.
And it was the first time. I was singing.
That's right. I was so surprised.
Yu-chan, Yu-chan.
The moment you said that, I felt like I was in the great Wook.
Yeah, yeah.
You felt it?
Yes, I did. And at that time, I didn't miss my words too much.
So even though I didn't miss my words too much, I could hear them so well that I was really happy.
So many people were calling me in Okinawa, so I could hear their voices.
Even though I didn't miss my words too much.
I was so happy.
Koha, too. I was so happy.
You know, Koha-chan.
I would have been happy if you called me Koha-chan. I thought about it a lot. I wondered what I should be called.
Yes, yes, yes.
With three letters, it's a good choice, isn't it?
There aren't many three-letter words, are there?
No, not really.
But, yes, I have been, you know, rehearsing? When we had this block investment in the lesson, I was like, "What should I do?
What should we do?
When I first introduced myself, I said, "Please call me Nen-Nen," right?
Yes, yes, yes.
But then we decided what to do about Yuchi and Yuyu, and I actually voted for them when I did a showroom video myself before,
I voted for it. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
In the end, when all the members decided which was easier to call me, I was called Yu-chan, so I became Yu-chan.
Oh, I see. So that's why you became YU-CHAI.
That's right.
I see. I didn't know that.
You didn't know, did you?
I see. Yu-chan is with Yu-chan.
That's right. Oh, but Ruri-chan, you know, they changed the song assignment, right?
Yes, yes, yes.
You were taken away, but how did you feel about that?
Well, I was happy. I mean, there was one time when a member was absent, and, you know, not much had changed.
Yes, yes.
I had a chance to sing once when one of the members was absent.
I did really well at that time, and the manager praised me a lot.
So I tried my best, but that phrase was really hard for me.
It went on for quite a while, so I wasn't satisfied with it, and I'm sure it's still there.
So I wanted to convey what I wanted to do better, and I felt a little frustrated about that.
But I was invited so many times, so I thought, "Thank you for inviting me like this.
It makes me happy. It makes me happy to be called by name, doesn't it?
I have some pictures of the show, and I'd like to show them to all of you who took them.
And now, let's go!
Emo!
It's Yuuchan!
It's Yuuchan, isn't it?
That's amazing!
It's Yuuchan, Anwina, she's beautiful!
You were saying earlier that this looks like Sora's icon.
I see. But I can see why.
Emo, emo, cute. What are you doing?
But it's definitely before "Overnight Limbo." It's a little melancholy.
Where's the connection? It's a bit like Wings.
It's Wings' number one, isn't it? The other one.
That's true, I think so. That's weird. That's cute. Let's move on.
Oh, Jell-O. It's an Indian burger. This is definitely an Indian burger.
Isn't the pink psyllium beautiful? Isn't the pink psyllium beautiful?
You can feel the audience's unity. That's it. A picture.
And Sora's holding out the mic like this. I love it.
I'd love to do it with everyone like this someday. I'd love to do something like this with everyone sometime.
Oh, okay? Go ahead and do it.
Okay, let's go next. Okay, Yuuchan.
She's so cute. She's having so much fun at the show.
She's raising her hand. What song is it? What song is it?
It's a music video. It's got hand shapes in it.
I wonder. Is that Yuuchan's hair in the back?
Is it overlapping? Is it Yuchan's hair, but someone's elbow in it?
Elbow in. Elbow in, right? Someone's elbow in.
Yes, it's in there. Cute.
Next... ah, gohada...
So cute! What's this?
Where is it? So cute!
He's so cute! His eyes are so big...
What's that sparkle on his head?
What's that on her head?
A pin? She was wearing a pin at the time.
A pin. That's cute. That's nice.
Next? Okay.
Ruri-chan. Ruri-chan, right?
It's Ruri-chan.
I'm guessing Cosmic Float.
No, I guessed wrong.
I was thinking maybe the love parade before the last pose?
Oh, yes, yes, before moving.
I'm wearing a new outfit.
Was it the same for Coulthon?
I was wearing a new outfit.
I had to buy a new chou chou, didn't I?
I have another one hidden under it.
This ribbon was from the first half of the first costume.
I forgot to take it off and it just came out.
It's my ribbon, but it fits, so I think it's safe.
That's the kind of thing. Let's move on.
Let's move on.
Oh, there's Ruri! It's me!
I look like I'm having a good time.
It's an encore T-shirt. It's an encore T-shirt.
Hey, it's the same name T-shirt as the one I'm wearing right now.
Looks like fun.
They look like they're having a good time.
You can't see it, but I noticed it, so I took off the ribbon.
I noticed and took off the ribbon.
Okay, let's move on.
So cute!
Little skin.
Encore.
It's an encore.
You can see the poka-poka.
Oh, my God!
Poka-poka.
Look at his face.
He's having a great time.
Yeah, he's having a good time.
He's so cute.
I think that's the last one.
Oh, there's more.
Teen spirit.
Oh, that's nice.
It was kind of the last song of Teen Spirit.
It was the last song of encore 5, the very last song.
They all look like they've done it, don't they?
Aren't they smiling?
Yes, they are.
Like, "Oh, yeah!
Like, "Okay, then.
That's a nice face.
Yes, I do.
You have a nice smile.
That's what it looks like... in the live pictures.
Thank you very much.
Well, let's see... in the comments.
You know, we both worked so hard.
We don't want you to praise us. We who don't want praise
Sure, we want compliments.
So will you guys give us compliments in the comments?
Will you?
Can you do that? Oh, good!
They're going to compliment us in the comments.
It was a great show!
Thank you very much.
I'm glad I said it was fun and cute.
Yay!
I'm so happy. Cute, cute, cute.
She's so cute. She's so cute.
So cute, so cute, so cute!
I heard it was cute.
So cute! So cute!
So cute!
Please give it back to me, everyone.
Give it back to me and I'll give it back to you and you'll give it back to me and you'll give it back to me.
Okay, let's move on.
The last one is past!
Oh, you were good again.
I want to see it again, you worked so hard!
I said no to the first song.
Emo... emo... emo...
Emo... emo...
I mean, they're all connected, you know?
I thought they were on par with everyone else, and I couldn't believe it was the first time I'd seen you on stage.
It was amazing.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
That was a great show. Thank you so much.
Thank you so much for doing such a great job.
You didn't get any cute comments at all.
I told you, didn't I? You didn't go through with it.
It says, "I can't stop crying.
Oh, no.
Don't cry! Don't cry!
It's a fun show!
This place has become more emo... and it's still emo!
Don't let your heart be in your mouth!
Yuko's heart is too strong today.
Is it strong?
Strong.
She said they brought in two of the best.
Yay!
We did our best.
I felt happy and fresh.
Yay!
They were fresh!
I didn't cry.
Oh, I didn't really cry.
I'm sorry.
I can only hope for a new Uka!
Yay!
We'll continue to work together as a group of seven.
I'm counting on you!
Unison has brightened up with the addition of Yuko's group!
Oooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo
I knew it! Your voice is still red!
But my voice might get better suddenly
Suddenly
I might suddenly lose my voice
Maybe tomorrow...
Good morning.
It's getting really low.
What if it's suddenly low?
Oh, Yu-chan, you've lost your voice.
Suddenly.
Slowly.
Good morning, Rui.
You're a little pale, aren't you?
But the fact that your voice still changes is proof of your youth.
Maybe I'll get a voice change.
You haven't yet.You haven't yet.
I haven't done it yet, and I might lighten up, too.
I might get high, right?
Maybe that'll happen tomorrow.
Yeah. - Yeah.
This is a little embarrassing. Let's not do this.
Let's not.
Hey.
You're looking at me like I'm a big sister.
It's gone.
Ru's being a big sister.
Yes, I know.
Everyone's doing it.
The best! The best!
The best! Thank you!
I'm counting on you.
I'm the oldest one here today.
That's for sure.
That's right.
He's in trouble.
What did he say?
You're not in trouble, are you?
No, I'm not in trouble.
Good, good, good, good, good.
It's okay if the pressure's too much.
No, it's not.
Everyone's nice to me.
I'm nice to everyone.
You're right.
It's written with something tsukkomi.
I just told Mr. blah, blah, blah, blah.
Who's in charge of commentary now?
Somewhere in there?
Rina-chan, isn't it?
No, it's me.
Yoo-chan? Yu-chan?
Next-generation ace, Tutsumi.
The next generation ace who makes a comment. Ace of the next generation of tsukkomi
That's what he calls himself.
Hmm?
Self-proclaimed.
No, Ruri's not the one calling herself that.
You're the self-proclaimed cute and coy one, aren't you?
That's right.
She's a business impostor.
It's kind of lonely here.
Why not?
You've got a good point.
Well, I guess that's about it.
Thank you for all the compliments.
Thank you very much.
That's all.
Let's take a look at the new visuals.
Let's take a look at the new visuals of the new costumes.
So...
Yes, sir.
We have a new visual of us.
Here it is.
Look at that!
It's cute!
I like it.
We did a little bit of comedy with this earlier, didn't we?
Right... look at this picture.
Ladies and gentlemen...
Look at Ruri.
Especially her feet.
Her shoes are cute, and so is her face.
If you take a look at her feet...
What, what, what?
They're cute, but...
You got a good look.
Yes.
What's up, Ruri? What's going on, Ruri?
She's floating in the air.
What's going on?
How can I take a picture of this?
I don't know.
It's so funny... like I'm Doraemon or something.
Doraemon?
It's got legs!
He's got his foot on my house.
My feet are on my feet.
My feet are on my feet!
Only the gladiatorial tune is floating a bit in the air while posing
Why? Why? Why?
Oh, he's going to float.
I think I finally mastered the art of floating.
During this time...
I'm making an amazing Doraemon!
I might have been Doraemon after all
I might have been Doraemon.
Yes, you noticed that earlier...
I was so surprised.
I didn't notice it before, but you did just now.
True half-view
Everyone, pay attention!
I'm listening.
Shall we look at the individual ones?
One at a time, please.
Yes, ma'am.
Yes, sir.
Okay.
Let's see what you just saw.
I don't know...
It's like that TikTok thing where you float around like it's going viral.
You know...
Like this.
The ones that make you look like you're floating in the air.
I might be able to do that.
I'll try it next time. Okay, then. One at a time, please. Okay, then, one at a time, please.
Okay, one at a time, please.
Ah, Yuri!
Yuri-chan is me, right?
Oh, no!
Yuri-chan is me!
Yuri-chan is an onion?
What's this? It's a curled onion.
Yes, it looks like an onion, but it's curled.
I tweeted about how cute I am on Twitter.
I got more likes than usual.
I got a lot of comments, and I wondered why people were responding to it.
I felt like I was saying to myself, "I'm embarrassed.
But I don't know...
She's good, isn't she?
Why are you saying yes?
Say yes! Say yes!
I think it's because her hand is on her stomach, like her stomach is cold.
Her belly comes out together.
That's right.
It's a "don't let your stomach get cold" pose.
You should be careful, too.
Maybe I should bring a belly wrap.
Sure thing.
Can I have a belly wrap for my birthday next year?
That's totally fine.
I was born in the summer.
Not at all.
Then I'll be waiting for a belly band next year.
Here's Sora.
Isn't she mature? This Sora...
It's too much.
Maybe a shoulder braid.
And you know what else? Sora had glitter in her hair.
Glitter.
Yes, she did!
This is making me want to do a comedy act! I'm starting to feel a little like I'm a big fan of this.
It's okay.
It's good.
I haven't thought about it yet.
You want to say something?
I want to make a big joke.
Raise your hand if you have an idea.
Okay, I'll do it.
I want to make a big joke.
I got a comment saying, "Sora mama!
You said "Mom.
I meant Sora.
I wonder what's for dinner tonight.
Oh, I see... that's a pose.
I wonder what I'm going to have for dinner tonight...
Because you're my mom.
Yeah, yeah...
What's for dinner tonight, Sora?
That's right...
Next...
Ah, Yoo-chan.
Yoo-chan...
What are you thinking about?
Nice smile.
That's a really nice smile.
I wonder what it is...
But it's like...
It's like this.
I don't know...
Like a young lady.
Like she's not happy.
But her legs aren't like that.
Don't they look a little half-up?
Yes, it does.
Depending on what you say.
It's a ponytail, actually.
But in my opinion, it looks a little like a half-up. But I thought it looked a bit like a half-up in my opinion.
Do you have any big joke?
A comedy?
Hmmm...
Mosquito bites.
Why?
I came here to comment and I got bit by a mosquito.
What do you mean?
Are you bitten by mosquitoes?
Uh, yes.
Oh.
You're crying your right eye out.
Oh, please stop that face.
I'm probably like that with everyone.
They all look a little different.
Actually, the eyeshades all have a little bit of crystal in them.
Stones?
Yes, they were all in different positions.
They were all in different positions.
And I was like...
It was like this.
That's right.
Like maybe you're not crying because of your right eye.
Only my right eye is crying.
You mean it looks like it's curling up?
I see.
Okay, Yu-chan.
It's like "Man-man-mae".
It looks like she's crying.
That's right!
It's like...
Next.
Next...
Momoa-chan!
It's Moa-chan!
Moa-chan's here, too, isn't she? Moa-chan is here too, isn't she?
That's right.
Are our pinky fingers overlapping?
They don't overlap.
Your pinkies are overlapping, Moa-chan.
It's so hard, so hard, so hard!
You're so cute.
Show us your forehead.
That's cute.
Yes, I do.
Well, are you a forehead-baring kind of girl? With bangs?
Yeah.
It makes you look a little bubbly.
That's for sure.
Which do you prefer?
Well, I like you with your forehead out.
I like it when you show your forehead at live shows, too.
I'm a forehead person too.
Oh, so you have a forehead, then.
You look like Rapunzel with your hair ornament.
It's the same with the atmosphere.
Let your hair down!
Let your hair down.
Oh, that's a "let your hair down" look.
Yes, I did.
I see. Now, please continue.
Yes, please.
Oh, Rina-chan.
There's a horse behind you, Rina-chan.
Yes, ma'am.
Merigoland.
Rina-chan, you dye your hair.
Yes, I do.
Oh, that's right.
But, you know, these are extensions, right?
Not yet.
Extensions. Extensions.
So cute.
Right?
I get the impression that Rina looks great with extensions, too.
What?
Rina-chan, at her recent live show, did you give her the outside sex tape or something?
You haven't done it for her?
You haven't, have you?
I don't mind.
You do Rina-chan's hair for her.
Yes, I'm always borrowing money.
That's right.
Yes, that's right.
I saw it.
I asked you. Did you see her belly? Rina?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You're good at that.
Yes, you are.
By the way, Momoa got Sora to do it for her, too.
That's right.
Moa-chan's hair...
Sit down.
Sit down... like a mother.
I saw your mom.
Yeah, I got it.
I got it.
Backstage.
What's this?
A fan
A fan.
Hee...
It's so hard...
Life is fun today, too Life is Fun Today
Life is fun today, too
Tariya and Tina-chan
It was!
Next
What's next?
Ah!
Okaruchan
What's wrong?
Isn't it short?
Too short.
What?
It's grown longer.
You mean it's longer?
It feels shorter.
Is it curly or long?
Is that what you mean?
Well then...
You're so careful, Maru-chan.
Yeah.
You're right, her arms are down.
It's on the side.
He's trying to say hello at school.
Nice to meet you.
Good morning.
It's a morning assembly.
This is a morning assembly.
Morning meeting.
Cute catsuit. Looks good on you.
It looks good on you.
Good morning.
Shall we continue?
Okay.
Mr. Arifuku.
Mr. Arriju? Mr. Ariju
Mr. Riju looks so chirpy here.
Yes, I do.
What do you think? Did I see a little?
But the tears are a little...
Didn't they look like this here?
Yeah, it's like...
No? Like a drop.
You look like that too, Riju.
She wears sparkles in her hair.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Blitter.
Lids.
It has a lid.
She looks like a goddess.
Like a goddess.
Yeah.
She's divine.
She has an amazing aura, doesn't she?
Yeah.
What do you mean?
I know.
It's amazing.
Beautiful.
Beautiful?
Okay.
You got it?
Yes, sir.
I'll make your wish come true.
Oh, that's good, that's good, that's good.
That's nice.
It's so god-like.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
So that's what our new visual is about.
Yes.
I'm looking forward to seeing the new visual.
Please do. Please do.
Yes, and on January 21st, at the manman live.
We performed our first song "Overnight Rainbow" for the first time.
We performed our new song "Overnight Rainbow" for the first time!
Yay!
We did it!
Overnight Rainbow!
That's right!
What do you think of the first performance?
Well, Rover Night Rainbow is...
First of all, the choreography itself... it's not the first time you've choreographed it, but it's the first time for me.
It's not the first time for me, but it's the first time I've been asked to join in the choreography.
The last pose, the part where all the other girls are doing it like this...
I was having a hard time with it, especially when I was doing it with my sister and I. We did it like this.
I think it's very important to pay attention to that part, especially at the live performance.
I thought it was really beautiful.
I like the bazaria harmony part of the choreography.
I think it's Sora and Rina who walk through it.
I think it's Sora and Rina who go through the middle of the bazaria harmony.
I did my best to match the timing and the two pairs on both sides.
I was in the lesson, but this time Koha and Ryo were next to each other, and I was with Koha and Sora was coming through.
Sora-chan was coming through...
But I forgot to give it to her.
And I'm Yuuchan.
Suddenly, she did this.
He said, "I'm coming through.
It's true, if I don't give it to her, she won't be able to pass.
I see... so that's how it is... the pre-release of "Overnight Rainbow" is now available, so please listen to it and love it.
It's time for the ending of FIERCK!
Oh, no!
The second episode of Ukka's Delightful Showroom is coming to an end in no time at all!
How was it? Last time there were 7 of us, but this time it's just me and 2 of us.
Are you okay?
I'm so glad to hear you're having fun!
I'm glad I got to know you two, because I didn't know you before, and we had a lot of behind-the-scenes stories about the show, so I'm sure you all had a good time.
How was it?
Now then, I would like to make an announcement from Ukka.Okay, then, I'd like to make an announcement from Ukka.
Yes!
Wait for me, everybody!
Wait for me!
Wait for it!
Here it comes!
Yes!
Two! Yes! Okay, Yu-chan, please! Yes! Yes!
Yes! THE JOURNEY BEGINS TOUR 2024 SPRING HOP STEP JUMP!
Yay! This is the fan club selection, and it ends today! Yes!
Here is the information about the first money of the tour! Amazing!
There will be a women-only area at all venues on the tour! Yay!
So please come out and join us, whether you are a woman or a man! Please come!
Also, for those who make it through the entire tour, what is that? An armband?
We will be giving away armbands to those who make it all the way through the tour.
Please come! Please come! We are waiting for you!
We are going to 9 stops in total, so you can come to all of them even if they are in your neighborhood!
Please! Please!
And the second one?
The second single "Overnight Rainbow" is now available for download!
Yay!
Yes, as I said before, Overnight Rainbow is now available for pre-sale, so please listen to it!
Please listen to it a lot! Please listen to it a lot!
And this advance...oh, yeah.
That's a lie.
The release of the album is on the 20th,
And to go along with the release on the 20th, we will be holding a release event!
Yay!
The first one will be held this Saturday, February 3, at the rooftop event space at Marui in Ueno, Tokyo!
The event will be held at the rooftop event space at Marui in Ueno this coming Saturday, February 3!
Yay!
So, I'm looking forward to it! I don't really know what it's going to be like...
Yes, but it's something, isn't it?
Yeah, but it's something, isn't it?
He said he'll decide at 9:00.
Yes, he did say that.
Will it be fun?Will it be fun?
I'm looking forward to it.
Please look forward to it until the day of the event. Please look forward to it.
Please do!
And on February 4, the next day, the next day, we will be at the event space on the roof of Magnet by Shibuya 109!
Yay!
And on February 10, we will be at a certain place in Kanagawa Prefecture, and on February 11, we will have a distribution event, so please come and join us!
Please come and join us!
Please check this page.
Yes!
Next!
Next?
Well, on February 17 at Tokyo Kineba Club, there will be a solo live performance for Moa Hoshiza's birthday in the first part, and for Sora Akane's birthday in the second part, so please come!
Please come!
I guess that's how I feel about the announcement.
Is that how it's going to be?
Yes!
Lastly, I would like to read the ranking.
I will.
Now, 5th place.
Fifth place goes to.
Issa-san.
Congratulations.
And in fourth place.
Risaku.
Congratulations!
The third place goes to
Janka-chan.
And the third runner-up is... Eri Eri.
Eri Eri-san.
Please give my best regards to her.
And the second place goes to. And the second place goes to.
Sorashido-san.
Mr. Sorashido.
Thank you very much.
And the first place goes to.
Shen administration.
Thank you very much.
And Ms. Dayne.
And now.
Please.
Thank you very much.
Ta-da!
Thank you, BB of Adonis.
Thank you.
Oh, oh.
I got the BB of Kawao Adonis.
Thank you very much
Thank you very much.
Yes, something like that.
That's all for this distribution.
The next transmission will be on Wednesday, February 14th at 7:00 p.m.
We will let you know who will appear on the show as soon as it is decided.
To make sure you don't miss it, please like us by clicking on the heart mark.
Please register to like us so that you don't miss any more!
Thank you!
Also, please check out our private webcasts.
That's all for now.
That's the end of the hilarious and huffing and puffing showroom of Ukka!
Thank you very much.
Please watch for the next show!
Thank you very much. Please.
That's all for now.
This is Ukka.
Bye-bye.